[Music]
Insurance Awareness Day
campaign was run in front of the gate under the aegis of ICC Lombard Purnia branch on the occasion of National Insurance Awareness Day. During this awareness
campaign,
people were given
all kinds of information related to insurance schemes by the comeos of ICC Lombard.
On this occasion, Collector Branch Manager of ICC Lombard
Sumit Sahi and Scenery Relationship
Manager Prabhat Kumar Sanhita of the company were
present. While talking to the media during this,
he told that the
main objective of this campaign is to make people aware about the
various benefits of investing in insurance schemes or policies.
Friends, the
campaign is being run. If
we have insurance then there is no worry.
We are making all the people here aware about the importance of
insurance that in today's date, insurance is not just for one person but for
a family.
In today's date, everyone saves money
but what happens, if any disease occurs
or any other type of insurance, we do it,
like you have health insurance,
your motor insurance,
your car insurance.  We also do home insurance, shop
insurance and all kinds of insurance. So the point
here is that we have to make people
aware. People here
lack awareness about what insurance is and why they
need insurance. You people also spend a lot of money and that is
savings. If
you fall ill, you
spend the same amount on anything, but the
same money can be saved if you take insurance and
pay a small amount for a year.
What happens in it is that they get coverage. A
person can be sure that
today I have signed up with ICC Lombard. If
anything happens to my family, if my Bhim family gets any
disease or there is any
expense for treatment purpose, then
what is that expense, ICC Lombard is standing to provide
them coverage for that expense.
We are running a campaign in front of the Dum office here.
We are also running another
campaign.
We have two campaigns going on in Girja Chowk.
My name is Sumit Shah, I am from here.  I
am a plaster branch manager, I have
seen it in Purnia and Bhagalpur.